It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
It's been a while.
お 久しぶりです
Because it's not a uniform.
制服じゃないから
When I change my clothes, I change a lot.
服変わるとだいぶ変わるんだ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
What have you been up to lately?
最近 何してるんですか?
I went to school recently.
最近は学校行ってました
busy?
忙しい?
busy.
忙しい
What about after you get back?
帰ってからなんですか?
After returning...
帰ってから...
I watch anime.
アニメを見ます
What happened?
どうしたんですか?
Saturday and Sunday?
土日?
It's one piece.
ワンピースです
Do you like it?
好きなんですか?
About 121.
121くらい
Is there anything wrong?
何変とかある?
It might be too complicated to remember.
複雑で思い出さないかも
What's the story?
どういう話なの?
Well, it looks like a science laboratory.
え っと、科学の研究室みたい
Everyone.
みんなで
There are a few different things.
ちょっといろいろある
670 is about 3 years later?
670って3年後の話?
yes.
そう
Two years later.
2年後じゃん
2 years.
2年
2年後
charm?
魅力?
Why should I watch it?
なんで見ちゃう?
It can be used in an emergency.
いざというときに使える
I like
が好きです
Are you strong?
強いんですか?
I have become stronger, but
強くなったけど、
I guess I'm weaker than everyone else.
み んなよりは弱いかな
In an emergency?
いざというときに?
It's like you can take a hit when the time comes.
いざというときに、一発かますみたいな感じ
Is it fresh?
新鮮かな?
It might be a little scary.
ちょっとね、怖いかも
Miscellaneous shower?
雑式おらし?
Yes, it's like a miscellaneous ceremony.
そう、雑式おらしみたいな
I'm wearing a pink mask.
ピンクのマスクつけてる
Looks like a cute character.
可愛いキャラクターみたい
Isn't it cute?
可愛くない?
可愛くはないかな
It feels like it's decided.
決まってる感じ
cool?
かっこいい?
cool.
かっこいい
A scary person came.
怖い人が来た
scared?
怖い?
It's a miscellaneous ceremony.
雑式です
Oh no.
やば
It's cute.
可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
The style is really nice, isn't it?
スタイルいいんじゃないですか、相当
No, not at all.
いや、全然
Can I have you stand for a moment?
ちょっと立ってみてもらっていい?
expensive.
高い
Tall.
背高い
It is 166.
166です
Is this 6?
これ6なんですか?
It's 6.
6です
Can I have you take it easy?
ゆっくりしてもらってもらっていい?
You have a good posture.
姿勢がいいんですね
Maybe.
かも
picture?
え?
There are more than 166?
166よりあるって?
lie?
嘘?
She's a really nice woman.
めっちゃいい女だわ
Oh no.
やば
It's so kind.
優しいですね
is that so.
そうですか
Do you play any sports?
なんかスポーツやってる?
Do it now...
今やって...
now...
今は...
I haven't done it.
やって ないです
Haven't you done it?
やってたんない?
Basketball parley.
バスケパレーとか
I was playing badmint.
バドミントやってました
It's really nice.
めっちゃいいですね
Your butt is beautiful.
お 尻きれいだね
I could fuck this ass for about an hour.
このお尻まじで1時間くらいもんでられる
No way.
やだ
Look this way.
こっち向いて
That's a nice outfit.
いい服装だよね
I feel like a young lady.
お嬢様って感じですね
Sure, it might be neat.
確かに、清楚かも
Do you live in a normal school or something?
正常学園とかに住んでる?
Do you live in a normal school?
正常学園に住んでるって?
正 常 学 園 に 住 んで る って?
surely.
確かに
surely?
確かに?
surely.
確かに
It's being processed properly.
なんかちゃんと処理してる
one piece?
ワンピース?
yes.
はい
It's ahead of One Piece.
ワンピースのまじ先してるね
Does it feel like wearing a dress?
ワンピースにかけてって感じ?
I guess you put it on.
かけてんだね
of course.
もちろん
He's an interesting kid.
面白い子だね
It's got really great style.
め ちゃくちゃスタイルいい
No, not at all.
いや、全然
picture?
え?
Are you a gravure idol?
グラビアアイドルですか?
Genes just happened.
遺伝子がたまたま
Your parents?
ご両親の?
that's right.
そうです
I'm grateful to my parents for this.
親に感謝だ、これ
Can I go back slowly?
ゆっくり返ってしまっていい?
Show me your back.
後ろ見せて
It wouldn't be strange if they appeared at Paris Fashion Week.
パリコレに出ててもおかしくないね
Maybe I'm exaggerating.
言い過ぎかも
But I'm happy.
でも嬉しい
It's really amazing.
本当にすごいっす
Self-control is good.
自制いいよね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Is Sato doing something?
佐藤がなんかやってる?
Sato: I haven't done it.
佐藤やってないです
TRUE?
本当?
It's good to have self-control.
自制いいからさ
I thought they were serving tea or something.
お茶とかやってるのかなと思って
Totally.
全 然
tickles.
くすぐったい
There's a main line on the side.
脇って幹線があるからさ
After all, you're sweating.
やっぱ汗かいちゃうんだよね
It's odorless.
無臭だね
I feel like it's the essence of a young woman.
若い女性のエキスな気がする
Please let me suck it a lot.
いっぱい吸ってもらって
Seriously?
マジで?
I like the mood.
ノリいいね
I'll smoke a lot, then.
いっぱい吸うわ、じゃあ
delicious.
おいしい
Is that so?
そうなの?
This is what I'm talking about right now.
これ今マンコン言ってるから
Seriously?
マ ジで?
This is amazing.
すごいよ、これ
I might have learned it for the first time.
初めて知ったかも
Because that's what I do.
そうにしてるから
What?
何を?
You understand, right?
分かるでしょ?
Because I'm not a child.
子供じゃないからさ
This is a nice side.
いい脇だ、これ
It's an armpit.
脇マンコンだね
Do you know?
知ってる?
This is how I do it.
こうやってやります
surely.
確かに
This is terrible.
やばいよ
do not.
しない
what up?
どうした?
Those are really nice-shaped boobs.
すごい形いいおっぱいだよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
happy.
嬉しい
That's terrible.
やばいね
It's perfect, everything.
パーフェクトだね、色々
thank you.
ありがとうございます
You're smiling, aren't you trying to hide your embarrassment?
笑ってるってさ、 照れ隠しでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
It's cute, isn't it?
かわいいよね、そういうの
When I say I'm crying, I feel nervous.
泣いてるって言うと、 気
I entered.
に 入ったよ
I liked it.
気に入ったよ
By myself,
自分でさ、
i don't know.
知 らない
Kuberb.
クバーブ
Is it that famous?
あんな有名な?
Kubarb wasn't in One Piece.
ワンピースにいなかったクバーブなんて
That might not be the case though.
それはちょっといないかもしれないけど
Try opening and closing it a little.
ちょっと開いたり閉じたりしてみて
The person who was arrested, now.
捕まった人、 いまして
YouTuber
Kubanah?
クバーナー?
Is this the case with the YouTuber who was arrested?
捕まったYouTuberが、 そうなの?
Now.
いまして
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Really?
本当に?
Yeah.
うん
a little bit.
ちょっと
Where was it wet?
どこを濡れ込んであった?
It was soaking wet.
濡れ込んであった
a little bit.
ちょっと
All, all.
全部、全部
That's appropriate.
適当だな
I can see it.
見えるよ
Stretch out a little.
ちょっと伸びて
It's so colorful.
すっげー色いよね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
this?
これ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I keep watching you get hit.
殴られてるとこ、ずっと見てるね
That's crazy.
めっちゃだね
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's delicious.
うまいですね
yes?
そう?
What kind of effort does it take?
どこの手間が?
It's time consuming.
手間が
Oh, that's amazing.
おー、すげー
When I look at it now, it's red.
今 から見てみたら赤になってる
It's true.
本当だよ
It's because it feels good.
気持ちいいからだよね
It came out great.
すげー出たね
I didn't have any work.
仕事ないしてたわ
You did something wrong, so I have to punish you.
悪いことしてたから、仕置きしないとだね
Once, once, it blows back.
一旦、一旦、吹き戻る